Guide to the Duke Ellington Oral History
Duke Ellington Oral History
Oral History of American Music
Duke Ellington Oral History
1939 1987
1977 1987
OHIII
Oral History of American Music
246 Computer Files
General
119 interviews as of September 9, 2021. This finding aid describes digitized copies of the interview recordings in this collection. Oral History of American Music also holds the original recordings, on a variety of legacy audio and video formats.
Scope and Contents
The Duke Ellington Oral History is comprises ninety-two interviews with and about Ellington, one of America's greatest composers. Included among the interviewees are musicians, family members, friends, and colleagues.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. The finding aid includes links to stream most interviews online via Oral History of American Music's (OHAM) AV access system, Aviary. Yale users can login to Aviary using their Yale University ID, to stream these interviews without restriction. Other users are able to request access to interviews directly through Aviary. For access instructions, and to request transcripts of an interview, see OHAM's website. This finding aid also includes links to Table of Contents for most interviews.
Some interviews may be restricted. Access to these restricted interviews may only be granted to a patron who has first obtained direct permission from the interviewee or their estate.
Some interviews may not have been digitized or are otherwise not available to stream online. However, these interviews may have been transcribed. Please see contact OHAM for more details.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically by surname of interviewee.
Jazz musicians; African American Composers; Ellington, Duke, 1899-1974
- Ailey, Alvin
  - Ailey, Alvin, 1983 September 7; OHIII 577 a-c; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 63 mins; Transcript Page Count: 60 pages
    Interview Location
    New York, NY
    Ailey, Alvin
- Anderson, Edmund
  - Anderson, Edmund, 1980 October 15; OHIII 550 a-c; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 99 mins; Transcript Page Count: 52 pages
    Anderson, Edmund, 1912-2002
- Ashby, Harold
  - Ashby, Harold, 1980 March 13; OHIII 542 a-b; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 64 mins; Transcript Page Count: 31 pages
    Ashby, Harold
- Avakian, George
  - Avakian, George, 1978 March 17; OHIII 517 a-b; Kolderie, Paul Q.; Approximate Running Time: 66 mins; Transcript Page Count: 28 pages
    Avakian, George
- Banks, Maurice
  - Banks, Maurice, 1983 September 29; OHIII 582 a-b; Tucker, Mark; Approximate Running Time: 91 mins; Transcript Page Count: 42 pages
    Washington, D.C.
    Banks, Maxine, 1921-2007
- Baraka, Amiri
  - Baraka, Amiri, 1977 October 4; OHIII 511 a-b; American Studies Class 430, Yale; Approximate Running Time: 89 mins; Transcript Page Count: 53 pages
    New Haven, CT
    Baraka, Amiri, 1934-2014
- Baron, Art
  - Baron, Art, 1986 December 18; OHIII 593 a-c; Tucker, Mark; Approximate Running Time: 124 mins; Transcript Page Count: 64 pages
    Baron, Art
- Beatty, Tally
  - Beatty, Tally, 1981 April 27; OHIII 566 a-b; Duke Ellington Society meeting; Approximate Running Time: 77 mins
    Beatty, Tally
- Bell, Aaron
  - Bell, Aaron, 1977 November 25; OHIII 502 a-b; Friedheim, Dan; Approximate Running Time: 91 mins; Transcript Page Count: 41 pages
    Larson's New York, NY
    Interviewer
    Dan Friedheim
    Bell, Aaron, 1922-2003
- Berry, Bill
  - Berry, Bill, 1977 December 2; OHIII 510 a-b; American Studies Class 430, Yale; Approximate Running Time: 90 mins; Transcript Page Count: 47 pages
    Berry, Bill
- Blake, Eubie
  - Blake, Eubie, 1973 October 1; OHIII 512 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 80 mins; Transcript Page Count: 27 pages
    Blake, Eubie, 1887-1983
- Brown, Lawrence
  - Brown, Lawrence, 1983 April 30; OHIII 584 a; Harrod, Dennett; Approximate Running Time: 13 mins; Transcript Page Count: 6 pages
    Washington, D.C. and Los Angeles, CA
    Brown, Anna Lawrence
- Brubeck, Dave
  - Brubeck, Dave, 1977 October 14; OHIII 505 a; Friedheim, Dan; Approximate Running Time: 33 mins; Transcript Page Count: 17 pages
    Brubeck, Dave (1920-2012)
- Byard, Jaki
  - Byard, Jaki, 1978 January 25; OHIII 509 a; Archer, Valerie
    Boston, MA
    Byard, Jaki
- Chertok, David
  - Chertok, David, 1979; OHIII 537 a; Orgel, Jeremy; Transcript Page Count: 14 pages
    Jeremy Orgel
    Chertok, David
- Cole, Martha
  - Cole, Martha, 1980 July 5; OHIII 545 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 61 mins; Transcript Page Count: 38 pages
    Tyringham, MA
    Cole, Martha
- Conaway, Robert
  - Conaway, Robert, 1984 August 24; OHIII 591 a; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 46 mins; Transcript Page Count: 24 pages
    Pittsburgh, PA
    Conaway, Robert
- Cook, Mercer
  - Cook, Mercer, 1984 May 31; OHIII 586 a-b; Tucker, Mark; Approximate Running Time: 45 mins; Transcript Page Count: 25 pages
    Silver Spring, MD
    Cook, Mercer, 1903-1987
- Courtney, Cress
  - Courtney, Cress, 1978 April 8; OHIII 525 a-c; Jacobowitz, Roy; Transcript Page Count: 15 pages
    Courtney, Cress
- Dance, Stanley
  - Dance, Stanley, 1977 November 22; OHIII 527 a-c; American Studies Class 430, Yale; Approximate Running Time: 91 mins; Transcript Page Count: 52 pages
    Dance, Stanley
- Dance, Helen Oakley
  - Dance, Helen Oakley, 1987 January 9; OHIII 594 a-b; Tucker, Mark; Approximate Running Time: 94 mins; Transcript Page Count: 47 pages
    Vista, CA
    Dance, Helen Oakley, 1913-2001
- Davis Wimp, Kay
  - Davis Wimp, Kay, 1980 July 21; OHIII 548 a; Oneppo, Martha; Approximate Running Time: 39 mins; Transcript Page Count: 18 pages
    Chicago, IL
    Davis Wimp, Kay
- Demme, Ken
  - Demme, Ken, 1979 December 27; OHIII 536 a-b; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 80 mins; Transcript Page Count: 42 pages
    Demme, Ken
- Dicks, Lillian Strayhorn
  - Dicks, Lillian Strayhorn, 1984 July 19; OHIII 588 a-d; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 153 mins; Transcript Page Count: 88 pages
    Roosevelt, NY
    Harriett Milnes
    Dicks, Lillian Strayhorn
- Driggs, Frank
  - Driggs, Frank, 1977 December 13; OHIII 504 a-b; Kolderie, Paul Q.; Approximate Running Time: 63 mins; Transcript Page Count: 43 pages
    Driggs, Frank
- Duke Ellington Fellowship Concert
  - Duke Ellington Fellowship Concert, 1977 October 14; OHIII 565 a-d
    Yale
    Duke Ellington Fellowship Concert
- Duvivier, George
  - Duvivier, George, 1983 August 18; OHIII 576 a-b; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 55 mins; Transcript Page Count: 30 pages
    Duvivier, George
- Ellington, Duke
  - Ellington, Duke, 1939 April 29; OHIII 500 a; Approximate Running Time: 4 mins; Transcript Page Count: 2 pages
    Konserthuset, Stockholm
    Ellington, Duke, 1899-1974
  - Ellington, Duke, 1970s; OHIII 500 b-c; Approximate Running Time: 45 mins
    Scope and Contents
    Multiple interviews. Part b includes interviews with Harry Carney and Ben Webster.
    Ellington, Duke, 1899-1974; Carney, Harry (19100401-19741008); Webster, Ben, 1909-1973
  - Ellington, Duke, 1963 October 30; OHIII 500 d-e; Cullen, Jack; Approximate Running Time: 107 mins; Transcript Page Count: 23 pages
    Vancouver, BC
  - Ellington, Duke, 1964 September 5; OHIII 500 f; Whitaker, Bing; Approximate Running Time: 49 mins
  - Ellington, Duke, 1973 February 1; OHIII 500 g; Parkinson, Micheal; Approximate Running Time: 63 mins; Transcript Page Count: 4 pages
    London, England
    Michael Parkinson
  - Ellington, Duke, 1964 January 14; OHIII 500 h; Williams, William B.; Approximate Running Time: 83 mins
  - Ellington, Duke, undated; OHIII 500 i-j; Cullen, Jack; Approximate Running Time: 61 mins
  - Ellington, Duke, 1958 April 5; OHIII 500 l; Seldes, Gilbert, 1893-1970
  - Ellington, Duke, 1964 May 13; OHIII 500 m; Littleton, Humphrey; Jones, Max, 1917-1993; Approximate Running Time: 93 mins; Transcript Page Count: 4 pages
    Tracks
    1. Jones and Littleton Interview 20 min, 2. Alistair Cook Tribute 14 min., 3. DE Interview, 1933 3 min., 4. Cleo Laine Tribute 4 min., 5.Dup of 500 j.
- Ellington, Ruth
  - Ellington, Ruth, 1977 November 11; OHIII 501 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 79 mins; Transcript Page Count: 50 pages
    Ellington, Ruth
- Ellington, Mercer
  - Ellington, Mercer, 1977 October 13; OHIII 521 a; Yale Class; Approximate Running Time: 44 mins; Transcript Page Count: 26 pages
    Ellington, Mercer
  - Ellington, Mercer, 1980 March 1; OHIII 521 b-c; Buckley, Dick; Approximate Running Time: 58 mins
    WBEZ, Chicago, IL
    Dick Buckley
  - Ellington, Mercer, 1979 July 22; OHIII 521 d; Caine, Daniel; Transcript Page Count: 6 pages
  - Ellington, Mercer, 1983 June 19; OHIII 521 e-f; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 71 mins; Transcript Page Count: 35 pages
- Ellington, Edward
  - Ellington, Edward, 1978 March 3; OHIII 523 a-b; Rosario, Sonya; Approximate Running Time: 50 mins; Transcript Page Count: 24 pages
    Ellington, Edward
- Ellington, Mercedes
  - Ellington, Mercedes, 1980 June 30; OHIII 547 a-b; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 78 mins; Transcript Page Count: 40 pages
    Yale Club, NYC
    Ellington, Mercedes
- Elliot, Lu
  - Elliot, Lu, 1981 May 17; OHIII 560 a; Archer, Valerie; Transcript Page Count: 23 pages
    Newark, NJ
    Elliot, Lu
- Gaskin, Victor
  - Gaskin, Victor, 1978 March 19; OHIII 516 a-b; Edwards, Marc; Approximate Running Time: 51 mins; Transcript Page Count: 21 pages
    Gaskin, Victor
- Gensel, Rev. John
  - Gensel, Rev. John, 1979 December 14; OHIII 540 a-b; Orgel, Jeremy; Approximate Running Time: 68 mins; Transcript Page Count: 28 pages
    Gensel, John, Rev.
  - Gensel, Rev. John, 1980 January 10; OHIII 540 c; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 26 mins; Transcript Page Count: 11 pages
- Grayson, Milt
  - Grayson, Milt, 1983 July 11; OHIII 573 a-b; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 56 mins; Transcript Page Count: 32 pages
    Grayson, Milt
- Greer, Sonny
  - Greer, Sonny [and others], 1979 January 1; OHIII 563 a-b; Crouch, Stanley; Approximate Running Time: 12 mins; Transcript Page Count: 5 pages
    General
    Additional interviewees include Nellie Lutcher, Hayes Pillars, Arthur Briggs, and two unknown people, as indicated in the table of contents. However, only Greer's portions of the interview are transcribed.
    Greer, Sonny; Lutcher, Nellie (19151015-20070608); Pillars, Hayes, 1906-; Briggs, Arthur, 1901-1991
- Gustar, Alfredo
  - Gustar, Alfredo, 1983 February 19; OHIII 572 a-d; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 156 mins; Transcript Page Count: 79 pages
    Gustar, Alfredo
- Hall, Adelaide
  - Hall, Adelaide, 1981 March 25; OHIII 558 a-b; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 54 mins; Transcript Page Count: 29 pages
    London
    Hall, Adelaide
- Hall, Barrie Lee
  - Hall, Barrie Lee, 1983 October 7; OHIII 581 a-b; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 63 mins; Transcript Page Count: 35 pages
    St. Croix, Virginia
    Hall, Barrie Lee, 1949-
- Hamilton, Jimmy
  - Hamilton, Jimmy, 1983 August 28; OHIII 580 a-c; Setlow, Kate; Approximate Running Time: 139 mins; Transcript Page Count: 59 pages
    Hamilton, Jimmy, 1917-1994
- Hammond, John
  - Hammond, John, 1978 April 3; OHIII 518 a; Kolderie, Paul Q.; Approximate Running Time: 42 mins; Transcript Page Count: 29 pages
    Hammond, John, 1910-1987
- Henderson, Luther
  - Henderson, Luther, 1981 July 9; OHIII 561 a-b; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 65 mins; Transcript Page Count: 33 pages
    Henderson, Luther, 1919-2003
- Henderson, Rick
  - Henderson, Rick, 1978 March 20; OHIII 522 a-b; Friedheim, Dan; Approximate Running Time: 69 mins; Transcript Page Count: 34 pages
    Henderson, Rick, 1928-2004
- Hentoff, Nat
  - Hentoff, Nat, 1978 February 28; OHIII 513 a-b; Ellington Class at NYU; Approximate Running Time: 73 mins; Transcript Page Count: 44 pages
    NYU, New York, NY
    Hentoff, Nat
- Hibbler, Al
  - Hibbler, Al, 1980 December 1; OHIII 553 a; Oneppo, Martha; Approximate Running Time: 69 mins; Transcript Page Count: 34 pages
    Teaneck, New Jersey
    Hibbler, Al, 1915-2001
- Hinton, Milt
  - Hinton, Milt, 1977 October 14; OHIII 507 a-b; American Studies Class 430, Yale; Approximate Running Time: 51 mins; Transcript Page Count: 38 pages
    Hinton, Milt
- Hovhanes, Alan
  - Hovhanes, Alan, 1983 May 1; OHIII 596 b-c
    Hovhanes, Alan
- Ibrahim, Abdullah
  - Ibrahim, Abdullah, 1979 August 7; OHIII 533 a-b; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 81 mins; Transcript Page Count: 29 pages
    Ibrahim, Abdullah
- Ibrahim, Sathima
  - Ibrahim, Sathima, 1979 August 10; OHIII 544 a-b; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 65 mins; Transcript Page Count: 38 pages
    Ibrahim, Sathima
- James, Michael
  - James, Michael, 1983 January 22; OHIII 570 a-c; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 123 mins; Transcript Page Count: 57 pages
    James, Michael
- Jewell, Derek
  - Jewell, Derek, 1981 March 24; OHIII 559 a-d; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 54 mins; Transcript Page Count: 29 pages
    London Times, London
    Jewell, Derek
- Jones, Jo
  - Jones, Jo, 1979 December 14; OHIII 535 a-c; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 142 mins
    Jones, Jo
  - Jones, Jo, 1976; OHIII 535 d; Speech at Ellington Class; Approximate Running Time: 24 mins
- Jones, Max
  - Jones, Max, 1981 March 24; OHIII 557 a-b; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 77 mins; Transcript Page Count: 34 pages
    High Gate, London
    Jones, Max, 1917-1993
- Joyce, John
  - Joyce, John, 1983 September 23; OHIII 579 a-b; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 49 mins; Transcript Page Count: 25 pages
    Joyce, John, 1939-2009
- Kerr, Brooks
  - Kerr, Brooks, undated; OHIII 526 a-b; Cook, Gene; Approximate Running Time: 59 mins; Transcript Page Count: 31 pages
    Kerr, Brooks
- Larkins, Ellis
  - Larkins, Ellis, 1980 March 27; OHIII 543 a-b; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 36 mins
    Larkins, Ellis
- Lewis, Elma
  - Lewis, Elma, 1978 March 23; OHIII 519 a; MA Elma Lewis School of Fine Arts, Roxbury, MA; Approximate Running Time: 40 mins; Transcript Page Count: 25 pages
    Lewis, Elma
- Logan, Marian
  - Logan, Marian, 1978 February 27; OHIII 524 a; Rosario, Sonia; Approximate Running Time: 47 mins; Transcript Page Count: 22 pages
    Logan, Marian
- McGettigan, Betty
  - McGettigan, Betty, 1980 June 15; OHIII 546 a-d; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 154 mins; Transcript Page Count: 74 pages
    McGettigan, Betty
- McPhail, Jimmy
  - McPhail, Jimmy, 1983 September 29; OHIII 583 a-b; Tucker, Mark; Approximate Running Time: 92 mins; Transcript Page Count: 46 pages
    McPhail, Jimmy
- McVicker, Carl
  - McVicker, Carl, 1984 August 23; OHIII 589 a-b; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 74 mins; Transcript Page Count: 54 pages
    McVicker, Carl, 1904-1993
- Metcalf, Louis
  - Metcalf, Louis, 1979; OHIII 538 a-b; Orgel, Jeremy; Transcript Page Count: 32
    Metcalf, Louis
- Michelle, Louise
  - Michelle, Louise, 1983 July 15; OHIII 574 a-b; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 89 mins; Transcript Page Count: 44 pages
    Michelle, Louise
- Mills, Irving
  - Mills, Irving, 1981 April 23; OHIII 567 a-e; Kahn Atkins, Irene; Approximate Running Time: 146 mins; Transcript Page Count: 35 pages
    Beverly Hills, CA
    Mills, Irving, 1894-1985
- Moore, Anita
  - Moore, Anita, 1983 September 21; OHIII 578 a-b; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 81 mins; Transcript Page Count: 38 pages
    Time-Life Building, New York, NY
    Moore, Anita, 1950-2001
- Morgenstern, Dan
  - Morgenstern, Dan, 1983 May 1; OHIII 596 a; Kennan, Bruce
    Morgenstern, Dan
- Morris, Gregory
  - Morris, Gregory, 1984 August 23; OHIII 590 a-b; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 81 mins; Transcript Page Count: 35 pages
    Morris, Gregory
- Morrison, Peck
  - Morrison, Peck, 1979; OHIII 539 a; Orgel, Jeremy; Approximate Running Time: 33 mins; Transcript Page Count: 22 pages
    Morrison, Peck
- Nelson, Dean Philip, WIlie Ruff, Duke Ellington
  Nelson, Dean; Philip, WIlie; Ruff, Duke Ellington
  - Nelson, Dean Philip, WIlie Ruff, Duke Ellington, undated; OHIII 549 a; Approximate Running Time: 6 mins; Transcript Page Count: 5 pages
    National Public Radio "All Things Considered"
- Norton, June
  - Norton, June, 1984 April 20; OHIII 585 a-d; Tucker, Mark; Approximate Running Time: 176 mins; Transcript Page Count: 100 pages
    Norton, June, 1894-1986
- Okin, Earl
  - Okin, Earl, 1981 March 19; OHIII 556 a-b; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 61 mins; Transcript Page Count: 31 pages
    Okin, Earl
- Oliver, Sy
  - Oliver, Sy, 1978 October 21; OHIII 531 a-b; Approximate Running Time: 66 mins; Transcript Page Count: 41 pages
    Anthony Coleman
- Pass, Joe
  - Pass, Joe, 1982 March 10; OHIII 564 a-b; Appelbaum, Larry; Dallman, Jerry; Transcript Page Count: 2 pages
    Annapolis, Maryland
    Pass, Joe, 1929-1994
- Post, Carl
  - Post, Carl, 1981 May 6; OHIII 528 a-b; Perlis, Vivian; Approximate Running Time: 87 mins
    Post, Carl
- Procope, Russell
  - Procope, Russell, 1977 December 2; OHIII 503 a; Jacobowitz, Roy; Approximate Running Time: 49 mins; Transcript Page Count: 13 pages
    Procope, Russell, 1908-1981
- Roach, Max
  - Roach, Max, 1978 January 25; OHIII 508 a-b; Edwards, Marc; Approximate Running Time: 62 mins; Transcript Page Count: 24 pages
    Roach, Max, 1924-2007
- Roche, Betty
  - Roche, Betty, 1982 November 19; OHIII 569 a-b; Milnes, Harriett; Transcript Page Count: 21 pages
    Roché, Betty
- Ruff, Willie
  - Ruff, Willie, 1978 April 4; OHIII 515 a-b; American Studies Class 430, Yale; Approximate Running Time: 55 mins; Transcript Page Count: 14 pages
    Ruff, Willie
- Sanders, John
  - Sanders, John, 1978 October 19; OHIII 532 a-b; Coleman, Anthony; Approximate Running Time: 88 mins; Transcript Page Count: 58 pages
    Sanders, John
- Sherrill, Joya
  - Sherrill, Joya, 1979 November 29; OHIII 534 a-c; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 110 mins; Transcript Page Count: 63 pages
    Great Neck, NY
    Sherrill, Joya, 1927-2010
- Singer, Arthur
  - Singer, Arthur, 1983 February 18; OHIII 571 a-b; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 83 mins; Transcript Page Count: 32 pages
    Jericho, NY
    Singer, Arthur
- Smith, Jabbo (Cladys)
  - Smith, Jabbo (Cladys), 1987 February 4; OHIII 595 a-b; Tucker, Marc; Approximate Running Time: 61 mins; Transcript Page Count: 26 pages
    Smith, Jabbo (Cladys)
- Stewart, Slam
  - Stewart, Slam, 1981 April 6; OHIII 555 a-b; Oneppo, Martha; Approximate Running Time: 79 mins; Transcript Page Count: 26 pages
    Binhamton, NY
    Stewart, Slam, 1987-
  - Stewart, Slam, 1981 May 16; OHIII 555 c; Oneppo, Martha; Approximate Running Time: 39 mins; Transcript Page Count: 28 pages
- Strayhorn, Helen and Carol
  - Strayhorn, Helen and Carol, 1984 May 30; OHIII 587 a-c; Milnes, Harriett; Transcript Page Count: 58 pages
    Strayhorn, Helen; Strayhorn, Carol
- Taylor, Malcolm
  - Taylor, Malcolm, 1977 October 14; OHIII 506 a; Jacobowitz, Roy; Transcript Page Count: 4 pages
    Taylor, Malcolm
- Terry, Clark
  - Terry, Clark, undated; OHIII 529 a; Friedheim, Dan; Approximate Running Time: 24 mins; Transcript Page Count: 12 pages
    Terry, Clark
- Tizol, Juan and Rosebud
  - Tizol, Juan and Rosebud, 1980 July 30; OHIII 562 a-b; Dechter, Brad, 1956-; Approximate Running Time: 58 mins; Transcript Page Count: 40 pages
    Los Angeles, CA
    Tizol, Juan, 1900-1984; Tizol, Rosebud
- Towers, Jack
  - Towers, Jack, 1978 March 17; OHIII 520 a; Approximate Running Time: 47 mins; Transcript Page Count: 22 pages
    Hyattsville, MD
    Towers, Jack
- Turney, Norris
  - Turney, Norris, 1978 February 28; OHIII 514 a-b; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 63 mins; Transcript Page Count: 44 pages
    Turney, Norris, 1921-2001
- Ulanov, Barry
  - Ulanov, Barry, 1981 February 3; OHIII 554 a-b; Orgel, Jeremy; Approximate Running Time: 35 mins; Transcript Page Count: 16 pages
    Ulanov, Barry, 1918-2000
- Valburn, Jerry
  - Valburn, Jerry, 1986 October 9; OHIII 592 a-d; Tucker, Marc; Approximate Running Time: 150 mins; Transcript Page Count: 74 pages
    Conditions Governing Access
    This material is restricted. Access may be granted to a patron who has obtained direct permission from the interviewee or their estate.
    Valburn, Jerry
  - Valburn, Jerry, 1987 March 19; OHIII 592 e-g; Tucker, Marc; Approximate Running Time: 111 mins; Transcript Page Count: 54 pages
    Plainview, NY
- Watkins, Tony
  - Watkins, Tony, 1982 November 19; OHIII 568 a-c; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 116 mins; Transcript Page Count: 55 pages
    Watkins, Tony
- Weston, Randy
  - Weston, Randy, 1980 January 15; OHIII 541 a-b; Archer, Valerie; Approximate Running Time: 73 mins; Transcript Page Count: 34 pages
    Weston, Randy, 1926-2018
- Wiggins, Bernice and Jaunita Middleton
  - Wiggins, Bernice and Jaunita Middleton, 1980 October 20; OHIII 551 a-b; Oneppo, Martha; Approximate Running Time: 60 mins; Transcript Page Count: 30 pages
    Middleton, Jaunita; Wiggins, Bernice
  - Wiggins, Bernice and Jaunita Middleton, 1983 September 6; OHIII 551 c-d; Tucker, Marc; Approximate Running Time: 88 mins; Transcript Page Count: 41 pages
- Williams, Francis
  - Williams, Francis, 1980 November 13; OHIII 552 a; Orgel, Jeremy; Approximate Running Time: 20 mins; Transcript Page Count: 7 pages
    West End, NY
    Williams, Francis
- Williams, Skippy
  - Williams, Skippy, 1983 July 15; OHIII 575 a-b; Milnes, Harriett; Approximate Running Time: 94 mins
    Williams, Skippy, 1916-1994
- Woodman, Britt
  - Woodman, Britt, 1978 August 9; OHIII 530 a-b; Dechter, Brad, 1956-; Approximate Running Time: 96 mins; Transcript Page Count: 45 pages
    Burbank, CA
    Woodman, Britt